Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
- Where did you get them from?
- His name is Albertini.
Ah. you see.
Gennarino in Praiano didn't have ovoline.
so he gave me the braids instead.
Then he gave me a bit of a discount.
Look here.
Who are you?
Daniel.
Daniel?
Your name is Daniel?
Daniel De Luca.
Thank you so much.
Your grandma was right about you.
Hi.
Eat.
Nice kid.
- Who the fuck is he?
- No idea.
Five euro. cash.
Don't worry.
What's your name?
Hassan.
Where are you from. Hassan?
Zuwara.
Do you speak Italian?
See you later.
What are we gonna do with Bruno?
My house is your house. DD.
Bruno. let's go.
Put it down. Come on.
Put it down.
Now fuck off both of you. go.
Who. Alice? No.
His name is Bruno.
Oh. please.
In the meantime. can I offer you a coffee?
Yes.
Hello?
Why? Do you think
there's something strange going on?
- Exactly. Bye. kid.
- Bye. Bignè.
Mum...
Coffee. tuna. bottarga.
tomatoes. mozzarella.
Tomatoes from where?
The owner. who is he? What's his name?
Thank you.
You're welcome.
- Who is Albertini?
- The tomatoes guy.
You have more luck than sense.
Alright. let's go.
Good morning. police.
I'm looking for Mister Daniel De Luca.
- Chief Maurizio Spagnuolo?
- Yes.
No. it's a different police station.
In Caserta.
Or perhaps lawyer Giraldi.
or Francesca...
Mister...?
Mister... I mean...
Superintendent Caserti...
Casertani.
So. so lovely to meet you.
superintendent Casertani.
Goodbye.
Listen. put these around your wrists.
No. Bignè...
Put them on. Quick.
His mother.
His mother?
I'm looking for Amina Younis.
This kid's mum.
This is Hassan.
I need to find Amina.
Come.
Amina is locked in a nearby building.
Thank you.
Don't make me lose my job.
Hi.
One second.
Why that evil face? Easy. I come in peace.
Nothing happened.
Go back to work. Africa.
Who are you? What do you want?
What the fuck are you doing? Let go of me!
My love.
Where is Alice?
Where did you hide my sister?
- Piece of shit! Where's Alice?
- My hair!
- Alright. alright!
Where's Alice?
- My hair!
- Enough!
Let's go. Go.
Asshole!
Hello?
- I'm coming back. dad.
- Alice?
I love you.
I love you too.
I'm waiting for you.
Good morning. princess!
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today